youlicense.com 2013-06-07

# Privacy Policy - YouLicense.com

Privacy Policy 

**Effective Date: November 18, 2008**

YouLicense, Inc. (“we, our or us”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive when you visit youlicense.com (the “ **Site** ”) and when you use any part of our service or software via our Site (the “ **Service** ”). 

This Privacy Policy may be amended or updated from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notice of these changes on our Site and in this Privacy Policy. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. 

**1\. Information Collection**

This Privacy Policy only applies to information you provide to us online while visiting or using our Site or the Service, or that we collect as part of the Service. It does not apply to information we have obtained offline or through other traditional means. Information you may provide in visiting or using our Site falls into two broad categories: personally identifiable information, and aggregate information. "Personally Identifiable Information" is information that is personal to you and which can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name, email address, financial information or mailing address. "Aggregate Information" is information that does not identify you, and may include, for example, statistical information concerning the web pages on our Site that users most frequent. Our Privacy Policy governs both categories of information, as detailed below. 

1.1 Personally Identifiable Information. 

We allow you to decide whether you wish to provide us with Personally Identifiable Information. Accordingly, we have structured our Site so that you may visit our Site, and review a range of information about bands, musicians and other materials relating to the music industry, without revealing your identity or providing any Personally Identifiable Information. 

One of our goals in creating this Site, however, is to enable bands and musicians to post information about themselves and their music, including but not limited to music, graphics, photos and sounds (“ **Content** ”) and to enable music promoters and other music professionals to access and conduct commercial transactions with respect to such Content, including the licensing and purchasing of various rights in the Content. 

In order to post any Content, perform certain transactions on the Site with respect to such Content, and in order to obtain access to certain other materials or information from our Site or portions of the Service, we ask that you become a registered user. Our registration forms will specify the information which you must provide in order to register and access and use certain features of the Site, including certain Personally Identifiable Information such as your email address, address and date of birth. 

When a user becomes a [paying member] of the Site, we collect credit card billing information including mailing address, and such other information as may be requested by us from time to time. 

1.2 Non Personally Identifiable Information: Aggregate Information 

Information concerning our users' activities at the Site such as which pages they visit, and how long they view these pages, date and time of the visit, and information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website such as your computer's Internet Protocol address, browser type, the web page you were visiting before you came to the Site - is Aggregate Information. This information does not identify a particular user, but does provide potentially useful data concerning our users' preferences and activities on the Site, and the effectiveness and interest of our Site's features. 

1.3 Cookies 

We collect Aggregate Information about your use of our Site through cookies and similar Internet technologies. "Cookies" are small text files that a website can use to recognize repeat users, to facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the website, and to compile aggregate data to improve the website and focus advertising. Cookies work as follows: we will send a cookie to your browser that uniquely associates your computer with information stored at the Site. Your browser places the cookie in its cookies file. When you next access the Site on your computer, the Site recognizes the cookie, makes the stored information available, and adds new information based on the present visit. 

You may choose not to allow us to collect information through cookies. If you wish, you can set your browser software to reject cookies, and most browsers provide instructions for disabling the cookies feature in their "Help" section. Because cookies can be used to provide certain functionality, if you disable your browser's cookies feature, certain elements of our Site may be unavailable to you. 

1.4 Advertisers' Collection of Information 

With Internet technology, it is possible for advertisers, as well as site hosts and other third parties, to collect information through the use of cookies and other technologies, such as so-called "clear GIF" files. We have no control over, and cannot necessarily protect against, the practices or policies of advertisers or other web site hosts using such technologies. 

1.5 User communications 

When you send email or other communications to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

1.6 Other Websites 

We offer and provide access to the Site and the Service in connection with other websites. Personally identifiable information that you provide to those sites may be sent to us in order to enable use of the Site or deliver the Service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from you.  Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that you submit. We encourage you to read the privacy policies and other terms of the other websites. ****

**  
****2\. Our Policy Toward Children**

We do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personally Identifiable Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at **admin[at]youlicense.com**. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personally Identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files. 

**3\. How We Use The Information that We Collect**

****  
3.1. Personally Identifiable Information

We use Personally Identifiable Information to (i) provide the Services, (ii) administer your use of the Site, the Services and your YouLicense account, (iii) personalize your experience, (iv) post your page on the Site and post other Content that you provide to us, (v) as provided below, (vi) ensure all users follow the Site's Terms and Conditions and other rules and policies, and (vii) for other purposes specific to our Site. In connection with postings you may request we make on the Site, users of our Site shall have access to such information - which may include your personally identifiable information. For example, your name, address, telephone number and/or email address may be included in your page on the Site or attached to a listing or other submission for contact purposes. 

From time to time, we also may use Personally Identifiable Information to us to provide you with information concerning newsletters, updates and other materials related to the purposes of our Site, or with information and offers for us or third parties that we believe you may find useful or interesting such as newsletters, marketing or promotional materials. We also will use this information to respond to questions from you, and to inform you of changes to our Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions or other rules or policies of the Site. You are free at any time to opt-out of receiving email and other information we may send to you by following the directions in such emails or communications. 

To advance the goals of our Site, we may link (a) your Personally Identifiable Information; with (b) Aggregate Information concerning for example your interests and preferences. Linking this information will allow us to create information packages and services that are better tailored to your interests and preferences. Among other effects, linking this information may allow us generally to improve and focus our Site. If we combine or link any information with your Personally Identifiable Information, the resulting combination will be treated as Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Policy. 

3.2 Non Personally Identifiable Information 

We use Aggregate Information for the above purposes and in order to monitor and analyze the Site (such as to measure our users' interest in and use of various areas of our Site, though many users are visiting our Site, and what areas of the Site present the most interest to our users), to improve the functionality, design and quality of the Site, to prepare statistical and other summary analyses of our users' behavior and characteristics, , for the technical administration of the Site and to investigate cases of suspected abuse. 

We may share Aggregate Information, and reports based on this information, with third parties unrelated to the Site including among others the general public for industry analysis, demographic profiling, other commercial purposes and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services. No such Aggregate Information that we provide to third parties will allow anyone to identify you. For example, we might report to unrelated third parties (a) the number of users of our Site; (b) the materials our users review while at our Site; or (c) the fact that "10% of our users use gmail." We may charge third parties for this information, and we may or may not limit the third parties' use of this information. We will use our reasonable best efforts to prevent third parties from attempting to make a connection between the Aggregate Information and the Personally Identifiable Information by, for example, seeking to combine it with other information. 

3.3 Cookies 

We use cookies to save your username and login password for future logins to the Site, to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor web traffic routing on the Site and aggregate usage of the Site. 

•  Both Personally Identifiable Information and Non Personally Identifiable Information 

•  Service Providers. We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the use of the Site, and to perform services related to administration of the Site (including without limitation bill and credit card payment processing, maintenance, hosting and database management services, web analytics and administration). These third parties have access to your Personally Identifiable Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated to comply with this Privacy Policy. 

•  Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas and administrative orders), pr [to protect our or a third party's property and rights or the safety of the public or any person] [to prevent or mitigate a threat of imminent harm to you or others, as is reasonably required in our discretion] 

•  Business Transfers. We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including among others your Personally Identifiable Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. 

**4\. How We Safeguard Information We Collect**

****  
We have put in place security systems designed to prevent unauthorized disclosure and use of your Personally Identifiable Information or private communications. These systems are structured to deter and prevent hackers and others from accessing this information. Due to the nature of Internet communications and evolving technologies, however, we cannot provide, and disclaim, assurance that such information and communications will remain free from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties who, despite our efforts, obtain unauthorized access.  
**  
****5\. How to Obtain Access to Information You Have Provided, And How To Remove or Change Your Information**

We make good faith efforts so all of our registered users may review, update, correct or delete the Personally Identifiable Information, if not required to be retained by law or for legitimate business reasons to the extent permitted by law. You may do so by contacting us at **feedback[at]youlicense.com**. Please be sure to clearly indicate your contact and data privacy preferences. We reserve the right to verify the identity of any person making an opt-out or correct/update request, but shall have no liability whatsoever resulting from false or erroneous requests. If you completely delete all such information, your account shall be deactivated. We may charge for such services, and may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes to the extent permitted by law. 

In addition, we may delete any information provided by you or related to you, pursuant to our policies as then in effect. 

**6\. International Processing or Transfer**

Your information may be processed or transferred outside of your state, where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. 

**7\. Contacting Us**

If you have any concerns or questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at admin[at]youlicense.com. 

Copyright © 2008, YouLicense,Inc. All rights reserved.
